u =[
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "благодарение",
      "Back": "thanksgiving; act of thanking"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "весна",
      "Back": "spring"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "весной",
      "Back": "in the spring"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "ветер",
      "Back": "wind"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "вокзал (нa)",
      "Back": "train station"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "время года",
      "Back": "season"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "гора",
      "Back": "mountain"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "градус",
      "Back": "degree(s)"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "дождь",
      "Back": "rain"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "зима",
      "Back": "winter"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "зимой",
      "Back": "in the winter"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "зонт(ик)",
      "Back": "umbrella"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "информация",
      "Back": "information"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "календарь",
      "Back": "calendar"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "климат",
      "Back": "climate"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "кyпальник",
      "Back": "women’s bathing suit"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "лес",
      "Back": "forest"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "лето",
      "Back": "summer"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "летом",
      "Back": "in the summer"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "лыжи",
      "Back": "skis"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "место",
      "Back": "place"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "море",
      "Back": "sea"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "мороз",
      "Back": "frost; intensely cold weather"
    },
    {
      "Front": "озеро",
      "Back": "lake"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "осень",
      "Back": "осень"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "осенью",
      "Back": "in the autumn"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "плавки",
      "Back": "men’s bathing suit"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "плащ",
      "Back": "raincoat"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "пляж",
      "Back": "beach"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "погода",
      "Back": "weather"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "приезд",
      "Back": "arrival"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "путешествие",
      "Back": "travel"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "снег",
      "Back": "snow"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "солнце",
      "Back": "sun; sunshine"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "электричка",
      "Back": "suburban train"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "январь",
      "Back": "January"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "февраль",
      "Back": "February"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "март",
      "Back": "March"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "апрель",
      "Back": "April"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "май",
      "Back": "May"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "июнь",
      "Back": "June"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "июль",
      "Back": "July"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "август",
      "Back": "August"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "сентябрь",
      "Back": "September"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "октябрь",
      "Back": "October"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "ноябрь",
      "Back": "November"
    },
    {
      "Type": "noun",
      "Front": "декабрь",
      "Back": "December"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adj",
      "Front": "грустный",
      "Back": "sad"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adj",
      "Front": "жаркий",
      "Back": "hot"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adj",
      "Front": "прекрасный",
      "Back": "wonderful; beautiful"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adj",
      "Front": "прохладный",
      "Back": "cool"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adj",
      "Front": "такой",
      "Back": "such; so"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adj",
      "Front": "тёплый",
      "Back": "warm"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adj",
      "Front": "холодный",
      "Back": "cold"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adj",
      "Front": "чудесный",
      "Back": "wonderful; fabulous"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adj",
      "Front": "готов",
      "Back": "ready"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adj",
      "Front": "одет",
      "Back": "dressed"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adj",
      "Front": "прав",
      "Back": "right, correct"
    },
    {
      "Type": "verb",
      "Front": "бывать",
      "Back": "to tend to be"
    },
    {
      "Type": "verb",
      "Front": "возвращаться/вернуться",
      "Back": "to return, go back"
    },
    {
      "Type": "verb",
      "Front": "гулять/погулять",
      "Back": "to stroll, take a walk"
    },
    {
      "Type": "verb",
      "Front": "загорать",
      "Back": "to sunbathe"
    },
    {
      "Type": "verb",
      "Front": "кататься на велосипеде",
      "Back": "to ride a bicycle"
    },
    {
      "Type": "verb",
      "Front": "кататься на коньках",
      "Back": "to skate"
    },
    {
      "Type": "verb",
      "Front": "кататься на лыжaх",
      "Back": "to ski"
    },
    {
      "Type": "verb",
      "Front": "купаться",
      "Back": "to swim"
    },
    {
      "Type": "verb",
      "Front": "получать/получить",
      "Back": "to receive"
    },
    {
      "Type": "verb",
      "Front": "собирать",
      "Back": "to collect, gather"
    },
    {
      "Type": "verb",
      "Front": "собираться",
      "Back": "to plan (to do something)"
    },
    {
      "Type": "verb",
      "Front": "узнавать/узнать",
      "Back": "to find out"
    },
    {
      "Type": "verb",
      "Front": "встречаться/встретиться",
      "Back": "to meet up (with each other)"
    },
    {
      "Type": "verb",
      "Front": "начинаться",
      "Back": "to begin"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adv",
      "Front": "весело",
      "Back": "happy, fun"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adv",
      "Front": "вообще",
      "Back": "in general"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adv",
      "Front": "грустно",
      "Back": "sad"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adv",
      "Front": "действительно",
      "Back": "really"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adv",
      "Front": "довольно",
      "Back": "fairly"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adv",
      "Front": "жарко",
      "Back": "hot"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adv",
      "Front": "обязательно",
      "Back": "surely"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adv",
      "Front": "отлично",
      "Back": "excellent"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adv",
      "Front": "пораньше",
      "Back": "a little earlier"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adv",
      "Front": "прекрасно",
      "Back": "wonderful, beautiful"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adv",
      "Front": "прохладно",
      "Back": "cool"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adv",
      "Front": "совсем",
      "Back": "quite; completely"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adv",
      "Front": "так",
      "Back": "such; so"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adv",
      "Front": "тепло",
      "Back": "warm"
    },
    {
      "Type": "adv",
      "Front": "холодно",
      "Back": "cold"
    },
    {
      "Type": "phrase",
      "Front": "если..., то",
      "Back": "if..., then"
    },
    {
      "Type": "phrase",
      "Front": "всего (+ number)",
      "Back": "only (+ number)"
    },
    {
      "Type": "phrase",
      "Front": "всё-таки",
      "Back": "nevertheless; all the same"
    },
    {
      "Type": "phrase",
      "Front": "Давай(те) (+ мы form of verb in future)",
      "Back": "Let’s (+ verb)"
    },
    {
      "Type": "phrase",
      "Front": "Давай(те) лучше ...",
      "Back": "Let’s ... instead"
    },
    {
      "Type": "phrase",
      "Front": "Здорово!",
      "Back": "Great!; Cool!"
    },
    {
      "Type": "phrase",
      "Front": "Идёт дождь.",
      "Back": "It is raining."
    },
    {
      "Type": "phrase",
      "Front": "ли",
      "Back": "if; whether"
    },
    {
      "Type": "phrase",
      "Front": "минус",
      "Back": "minus"
    },
    {
      "Type": "phrase",
      "Front": "на улице",
      "Back": "outside"
    },
    {
      "Type": "phrase",
      "Front": "(не) так(ой) ..., как ...",
      "Back": "(not) as ... as ..."
    },
    {
      "Type": "phrase",
      "Front": "неужели",
      "Back": "Really ...?"
    },
    {
      "Type": "phrase",
      "Front": "по Цельсию",
      "Back": "in Celsius"
    },
    {
      "Type": "phrase",
      "Front": "по Фаренгейту",
      "Back": "in Fahrenheit"
    },
    {
      "Type": "phrase",
      "Front": "Приезжай(те)/Приxoди(тe) в гости.",
      "Back": "Come for a visit."
    },
    {
      "Type": "phrase",
      "Front": "Светит солнце.",
      "Back": "The sun is shining."
    }
  ]
